<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Martha Trippin]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Martha Trippin]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/martha-trippin/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 15:56:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/martha-trippin/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Civil Rights]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Civil Rights</h1><p>When I was a kid history was boring as snot. I had to fight to stay awake in class and it wasn’t until college that I finally figured out “my” way of getting through it. My brother and I were both fans of Star Trek so of course I watched every episode that came on our 5 channel television. I knew who the good guys were and who the bad guys were so once in college and taking a history class I figured out that if I related what ever battle we were studying to Star Trek then at test time I was golden. Who ever the bad guys were, in my mind they were the Ramulans and of course you know who the good guys were if you were a Trek fan.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ad0882f9-cd9b-4322-8e81-1eeef08eb266.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ad0882f9-cd9b-4322-8e81-1eeef08eb266.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">18931acb-3098-48c8-b7a3-240a9266157c</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 15:55:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Los Alamos, New Mexico]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Los Alamos, New Mexico</h1><p>The drive from Santa Fe to Los Alamos was quick and full of sights. Los Alamos sits on top of a mountain and has a very explosive history. Our first stop was theBradbury Museum. We learned all about the making of the atomic bomb and the history of Los Alamos National Laboratory.From there we explored the town for a little bit in search for some atomic bomb souvenirs and then headed toBandelier National Monument in Frijoles canyon.We camped in the parking lot of the Visitor's Center. They actually had RV camping which was nice. We woke up early the next morning ate our breakfast in the EP, bought our park entrance tickets and waited for the bus ride up.We had a fabulous time hiking around Bandelier and learning about the cliff dwellings we even climbed the 140ft (up 4 ladders and several stone staircases) to Alcove house.(Checking out the view! LOL!)Before leaving Santa Fe we had to make a quick pit stop for new hiking boots, paired with our awesome socks that we bought at a boutique on the Plaza, just perfect for hiking at Bandelier.(Heading back down the 140 ft. climb to Alcove house)Anywhere that the boys could romp and run free was an excellent stop. The first cliff dwellings that you come to on the hike to Alcove house had lot of rocks, holes and tight spots that the kids could have played in all day. There was even a little steam that we had to cross that the kids enjoyed.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9fa9bb4f-8501-40ca-8dd4-f633d95e0637.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9fa9bb4f-8501-40ca-8dd4-f633d95e0637.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c5a3cfc8-0a9c-4fed-b44b-0697f44707a6</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 14:33:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Techies Project by Photographer Helena Price]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Techies Project by Photographer Helena Price</h1><p>The two words "Silicon Valley" immediately stir up stereotypes, stigma and maybe an HBO show. The name has become a cultural reflex, and that's what photographer Helena Price wants to change with her ambitious, large-scale portrait and interview series. Techies Project, launched today, is a collection of 100 in-depth interviews that breaks this idea of the "sameness" plaguing the area.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a7265c5abd944ed7ad3fdd9c9b6270021b13537b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/culture/techies-project-silicon-valley-interviews</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1406f3b1-9aea-4de1-83b6-d34b49dfd517</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 14:28:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New SpaceX landing photos make you feel like the rocket is coming down on top of you]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>New SpaceX landing photos make you feel like the rocket is coming down on top of you</h1><p>Up until now, we've really only seen SpaceX's rocket landing in the middle of the ocean from afar. Chase planes near the drone ship provided a spectacular view of the milestone event, but now, S...</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/aaef34df6ca9a285c5bdf2adaf9b1abfcc018b79.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.theverge.com/2016/4/12/11415518/spacex-rocket-landing-close-up-photos-falcon-9</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2e93f4c8-42e4-4470-9f8a-196882d66460</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 14:28:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Beautiful Speedometer for Bikes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A Beautiful Speedometer for Bikes</h1><p>Shout-out to designers who are also obsessed with cycling because their work frequently results in something new and clever, like the arresting Omata One. Mounted onto a bike, the speedometer's unique analog face informs of the four most relevant ride metrics (speed, distance, ascent and time).</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d105236023603a813c26d257fbe058ad72b3f663.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/tech/omata-one-analog-gps-speedometer-cycling-kickstarter</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7893fcec-fa3d-41d0-8042-026a4b00aee1</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 14:28:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>